{
  "qid": "QomeO",
  "name": "Jeremiah Samuel",
  "questions": [
    {
        "question": "What book has impacted Jeremiah Samuel the most?",
        "options": [
            "The Phsycology of Money",
            "Atomic Habits",
            "48 Laws of Power",
            "Don't Belive Everything You Think",
            "3AM Questions",
            "Think and Grow Rich",
            "Rich Dad Poor Dad"
        ],
        "color": 3,
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Jeremiah Samuel like to cook?",
        "options": [
            "Loves it",
            "Sometimes",
            "Not at all"
        ],
        "color": 4,
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Jeremiah Samuel's Biggest Fear?",
        "options": [
            "Doesn't Have Any",
            "Love",
            "People",
            "Money"
        ],
        "color": 1,
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Jeremiah Samuel's Primary Motivation In Life?",
        "options": [
            "Making His Parents Proud",
            "Being Able to Flex on Everyone",
            "Getting Rich Quick",
            "Knowing that there is noone who cares"
        ],
        "color": 6,
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Jeremiah Samuel value most in a Relationship?",
        "options": [
            "Loyalty and reliability",
            "Open communication and honesty",
            "Shared interests and experiences",
            "Empathy and understanding",
            "Super Speed"
        ],
        "color": 0,
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How would Jeremiah Samuel define success?",
        "options": [
            "By reaching specific goals and milestones",
            "By feeling content and fulfilled in life",
            "By having a positive impact on others",
            "By achieving a balance between various aspects of life",
            "Being SUPER rich"
        ],
        "color": 0,
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Jeremiah Samuel's Response to FAILURE",
        "options": [
            " It motivates him to work harder and prove the failure wrong",
            " He tends to feel discouraged",
            "He Sees it as inevitable",
            "Changes Him forever",
            "Doesn't care moves on"
        ],
        "color": 6,
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "How does Jeremiah Samuel define FORGIVENESS",
        "options": [
            "Letting go of resentment and finding peace within oneself",
            "Excusing someone's actions without addressing the harm caused",
            "Rebuilding trust and repairing relationships after a betrayal",
            "Avoiding conflict and pretending that everything is okay",
            "Always being the nicest you can be care and never hold a grudge"
        ],
        "color": 4,
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "How many TRUE NONBACKSTABBING FRIENDS does Jeremiah Samuel have?",
        "options": [
            "15",
            "2",
            "1 (One significant person)",
            "0 (Only Has Himself)"
        ],
        "color": 6,
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Just For Fun What is THE BEST General Purpose Programming Language",
        "options": [
            "Rust ftw",
            "JavaScript on Top",
            "Java cuz it tastes good",
            "Python since its ez"
        ],
        "color": 7,
        "answer": 1
    }
],
  "langloc": "NA-EN",
  "creator": "9SZTzoJnqORliInd92DoFri7DDz1"
}